Coming, coming! Operation Delta has stepped up its game again and is giving away legendary weapon bundles for free. Can you bear this?
The conditions for receiving it are also very simple. You only need to complete the designated tasks starting from August 8th.
You can choose one of the three newly launched bundles, and you can get a total of two sets during the event.
Brothers! The treasures hidden in this event are even more impressive.
Search the designated container on the map for a chance to obtain a treasure map.
You can also get treasure maps and Big Red big gold from the treasure hunting team, brothers!
If you happen to drive to map No. 8, then fine, you just need to find the treasure map location, Big Red and you have it!
This Treasure Hiding Month event is held on three maps: Dam, Changgong, and Bakeshi Treasure Locations.
Longlong has marked it for everyone, and all kinds of big red are waiting for you! Pay attention to Longlong, the specific location behind,
Dragon Dragon will also run out for everyone.